A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1972-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 31515], 1970-1981, Extent: cu. ft. (boxes). (Box 1-)
  - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 100)
  - Federal budget, 1981 Fiscal year (Box 101)
  - Health, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Health Regulatory Board, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Health Services Cost Review Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Service, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - State Advisory Office, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Visually handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Volunteerism, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Study of Duplication and Undue Competition, Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Financial Subcommittee Commission on Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Dept. of Health, Agency Guidance Memorandum, 1980-1982 (Box 101)
  - Budget, 1980-1982 (Box 101)
  - Special Education, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Program Indicators, 1978-1981 (Box 101)
  - Rules for the Administration of the Virginia Personnel Act (of 1942), 1977 (Box 101)
  - Capital Outlay Progress Report, 1980-1982 (Box 101)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 101)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 101)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 102)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 102)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 102)
  - Secretary of Human Resources, Dr. Jean L. Harris, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 102)
  - Budget, 1981 (Box 102)
  - Prevention of Psychosocial Disorders in Infancy in Appalachia, 1980 (Box 102)
  - Plan for the Development of a Statewide Program for the Prevention of Mental Illness, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse in Virginia, Implementation Report, 1981 (Box 102)
  - Plan for the Development of a Statewide Program for the Prevention of Mental Illness, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse in Virginia, Draft, 1978-1981 (Box 102)
  - Budget, 1981-1984 (Box 102)
  - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 103)
  - Block Grants to States for Health Services, 1981 (Box 103)
  - Attorney General, Office of, The Civil Digest newsletter, 1977-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Transportation (Fogarty), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Public Safety (White), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy (Connock), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Education (Castelle), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources (Diener), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Administration and Finance (Anderson), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Cabinet, Duties and Responsibilities, 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Congress, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Attorney General, Office of, General (Baliles), 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Commission on Family Life (SJR 79), 1978 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, House Appropriations Committee, 1978 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, JLARC, 1978-1981 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Legislation affecting Human Resource Agencies, 1982 (Box 104)
  - General Assembly, Commission on Mental Health and Mental Retardation (HB 1935), 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Study of Needs of Medically Indigent Children (HRJ 55), 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Legislative Implementation Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Local and Regional Special Education Facilities Task Force to Study the Establishment of Local and Regional Special Education Facilities (HB 264), 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Mandated programs, 1977 (Box 105)
  - Governor, General, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor Robb, Transition issues, 1982 (Box 105)
  - Governor Dalton, Executive orders, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor, Cabinet meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor Robb, News summaries, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor Dalton, News summaries, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor, Organizational memberships policy, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor, Policy memoranda, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor, Proclamations, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor, Special Assistant for Constituent Affairs (Ben Dendy), 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - Governor, State owned aircraft charges, 1978-1981 (Box 105)
  - General Assembly, Local Option (SB 160), 1978 (Box 106)
  - General Assembly, MHMRSA Prevention Plan (SJR 10), 1978-1981 (Box 106)
  - General Assembly, Southwestern State Task Force (SJR 283), 1978-1981 (Box 106)
  - Block grant program, 1982 (Box 106)
  - General Assembly, Governor's Toxic Substance Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 106)
  - Governor, State Occupational Information Coordinating Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 106)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Council for the Deaf, 1978-1981 (Box 107)
  - Working Committee on Emotionally Disturbed Children (DDPC), 1978-1981 (Box 107)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Developmentally Disabled Protection and Advocacy, OCR Complaint, 1978-1981 (Box 107)
  - Human Resources, Office of, VOcational Rehabilitation, National Academy for Rehabilitation, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Vocational Rehabilitation, Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, Sheltered Workshops, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, Woodrow Wilson Rehab Center, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, State Office on Volunteerism, General, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Commission on the Status of Women, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Advisory Committee on Emergency Medical Services, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Advisory Hospital Council, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Mental Health and Mental Retardation Professional Advisory Board, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Long Term Care Gerontology Center, Advisory Council (VCU Center of Aging), 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Radiation Advisory Board, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Visuallly Handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Block grants, 1978-1981 (Box 108)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, General, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, Virginia Board of Dentistry, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Medicine, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Nursing, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, Board of Examiners in Optometry, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Pharmacy, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Regulatory Boards, State Board of Veterinary Examiners, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Health Services Cost Review Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Vocational Rehabilitation, Conference on Handicapped Individuals, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, Division of Information Services, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Rehabilitative Services, International Year of Disabled Persons, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Vocational Rehabilitation, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, General, 1978-1981 (Box 109)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Health Care in MHMR Institutions and Corrections Facilities, 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Bureau of Health Education, 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Health Plan and Resource Development (HSA), 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Long Term Care, 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Information Bulletins, 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, National Health Insurance, 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Medical Assistance Program (Medicaid), 1978-1981 (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, State Perinatal Services Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Personnel, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Bureau of Shellfish Sanitation, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Pharmacies, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Statewide Health Coordinating Council, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Special Health Services, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Nutrition Program, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Division of Solid and Hazardous Wastes, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Toxic Substance Information Act, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Vector Control, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Virginia Environmental Endowment (Kepone), 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Division of Water Programs, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, WIC Program, 1978-1981 (Box 111)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Balance of State Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, State Board of Health, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Certificate of Need Program, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Bureau of Crippled Children, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Health, Emergency Medical Services, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Virginia Block grants, 1978-1981 (Box 112)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Vocational Rehabilitation Board, 1978-1981 (Box 113)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Loose correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 113)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, General, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Welfare, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Other State Agencies, Management Analysis and Systems Development, Forms Management Program, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Other State Agencies, Marine Resources Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Other State Agencies, Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Personnel and Training, General, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Personnel and Training, Equal Employment Opportunity Program, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Personnel and Training, Grievance Procedure, 1978-1981 (Box 114)
  - Secretary's Files, Miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda, 1981 (Box 115)
  - Secretary's Files, Miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda, 1981-1982 (Box 116)
  - Secretary's Files, Miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda, 1980-1982 (Box 117)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 117)
  - Other State Agencies, Office of the Comptroller, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Corrections, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Virginia State Crime Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Education, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, State Office of Emergency and Energy Services, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Office of Employee Relations Counselors, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Council on the Environment, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of General Services, Engineering and Buildings, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of General Services, Division of Purchases and Supply, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of General Services, Office of Risk Management, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, State Council on Higher Education, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Highways and Transportation, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Housing and Community Development, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Justice and Crime Prevention, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Division of Legislative Services, 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD), 1978-1981 (Box 118)
  - Other State Agencies, Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, Sec. of Commonwealth, 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, Virginia Institute of Marine Sciences (VIMS), 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, Virginia Community Colleges, 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, Virginia Commonwealth University, 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, Virginia Telecommunications Council, 1978-1981 (Box 119)
  - Other State Agencies, 1978-1981 (Box 120)
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 32692], 1982-1986, Extent: 17 cu. ft. (17 boxes). (Box 1-17)
  - Agency files, Aging, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Aging, Long Term Care Council, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Aging, Governor's Advisory Board on Aging, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Children Division, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Deaf, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, General, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, File No. 6, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, Affirmative Action Plan, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, Audit, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, GETD, Private Industry Council, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Asbestos, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Audit, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, State Board of Health, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Certificate of Need, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Certificate of Need, Annual report, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Certificate of Need, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Comm. Health Service, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Health Planning and Resource Development, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Medical and Nursing Facilities Services, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Review of Existing Regulations, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Shellfish Sanitation, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Solid and Hazardous Waste, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Uranium, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health, Water supply, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Boards, Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Boards, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Boards, Budget, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Boards, Management criticism, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Boards, Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Regulatory Boards, Optometry, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost Review Council, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Indians, Commission on, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, MAS, Medicaid Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, MAS, Medicaid Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Audit, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Indigent Health Care, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Medicaid, Mary Washington Hospital, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Medicaid, "Use of the CPI Escalator for Nursing Home Reim.," 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Organ Transplant, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Unit Dose, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Waivers, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MAS, Mgt. study, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Task Force, "Needs of Mentally Ill Children," 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Audit, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Board, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Community Service Boards, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Development Disabled Plan Council, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Committee on Housing for the Disabled, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Governor's Management Assessment Team Report, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, "Action for Prevention," 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Corrections Training Academy (SSVTC), 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, SSVTC, General, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Central State Hospital, General, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Office of Substance Abuse, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, Va. Treatment Center, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, MHMRS, WSH, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Mobile Rehab. Engr. Unit, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, DRS, Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Affirmative Action Program Assessment, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, DRS Board, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, "Independent Living," 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Medical Only Services Program, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Sheltered workshops, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Spinal cord injury, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, Va. Head Injury Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitation Services, WWRC, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Advocacy Dept. for the Developmentally Disabled, CAP, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Advocacy Dept. for the Developmentally Disabled, Va. Board for Rights of the Disabled, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, ADC, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Committee on Family Violence, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Community Action Agencies, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Employment Service Program, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Family and Children's Trust Fund, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Foster parents, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Fuel assistance, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Low Income Home Energy Assistance Grant, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Care, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Fiscal Management Bureau, 1982-1984 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Social Services, "A Model Act Regulating Board and Care," 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Food Stamp Program, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Info. Officer newsletters, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Legal services, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Legislation, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Neighborhood Asst., 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Refugee Resettlement, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Title XX, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Rape Crisis Treatment and Prevention, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Victims of Crime, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, Constituent correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, Audit, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, Library, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, Personnel (Review for privacy), 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Volunteerism, Dept. of, General Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Women, Council on the Status of, General, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Women, Council on the Status of, Prog. Proposal Report, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
  - General files, Agency Clusters correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Executive agreements, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, HRA, Organizational memberships, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, SIAG (Sec. Info. and Ana. Group), 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Agency heads evaluations (Review for privacy), 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Secretary's Advisory Council, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Duke University, Executive Education Program, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Evaluation Group, Secretary's, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, AA/EEO, Technical Advisory Group on Interagency Coordination Committee on Del. Service to Handicapped children, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Agency Profiles, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, New Directions, HR Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Newsclippings, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, Office supplies and requisitions, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, "Due Date Monitoring Reports," 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, HRA, Health costs, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - General files, HRA, General correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Sewage Handling and Disposal Regulations, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Administration, Sec. of, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Duties and responsibilities, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Commerce and Resources, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Finance, Sec. of, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Education, Sec. of, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Audit report, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Administration and Finance, Sec. of (Anderson), 1982 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Financial Policy, Asst. Sec of. (Connock), 1982 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Public Safety and Transportation (White), 1984 (Box 2)
  - General files, Cabinet, Public Safety and Transportation, 1982 (Box 2)